https://navisyachtcharter.com/nyc-privacy-statement

HomeBookingSitemapCharterLuxury Yachts Croatia Sailing Yachts CroatiaCatamarans CroatiaSailing Yachts GreeceCatamarans GreeceGulets CroatiaLuxury YachtsGreece CharterMediterranean CharterCrewed Sailing Yachts GreeceLuxury Sailing Yachts MediterraneanFeaturedItinerary & DestinationsItinerarySuggested Sailing Routes in CroatiaSuggested itinerary for South-central DalmatiaSuggested itinerary for North DalmatiaSuggested itinerary for GreeceDestinationsYacht charter BahamasYacht charter CaribbeanYacht charter Italy and FranceYacht charter SpainYacht charter TurkeyAboutNYC
About NYCCareersYacht ManagementTerms, Conditions & Contracts
TermsConditionsMYBA ContractHYBA ContractAdditional Information
About CroatiaMarinas in CroatiaAbout GreeceLinksVIP ServicesExecutive protectionVIP carsPrivate jet servicesEvents CharteringNewsContact Us
NYC Privacy Statement Navis Yacht Charter company is commited to protect your privacy.When accessing our Website, Navis Yacht Charter will learn certain information about you during your visit. How we will handle information we learn about you depends upon what you do when visiting our site.If you visit our site to read or download information on our pages, we collect and store only the following information about you:1. The name of the domain from which you access the Internet 2. The date and time you access our site 3. The Internet address of the website you used to link directly to our site.If you identify yourself by sending us an e-mail containing personal information, then the information collected will be solely used to respond to your message.The information collected is for statistical purposes. Navis Yacht Charter may use software programs to create summary statistics, which are used for such purposes as assessing the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, what information is of most and least interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas.For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, Navis Yacht Charter uses software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.Navis Yacht Charter will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us, nor will such information be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without the approval of the user at the time of collection. NYC website contains links to third party websites. NYC is not responsible or liable for any content, advertising, products or other materials available from such third party sites. User also agrees that NYC shall not be liable for any loss or damage of any sort by visiting such pages. Yachts ( Yacht charter ) listing details are belived to be true but not guaranteed by NYC – Yacht charters.Please contact us for any informations in regads to this privacy statement . This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. Data protectionWe are very pleased about your interest in our company. Data protection is of particular importance for the management of Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo. A use of the web pages of the Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo is basically possible without any indication of personal data. However, if an affected person wishes to use our company’s special services through our website, personal data processing may be required. If the processing of personal data is required and there is no legal basis for such processing, we generally seek the consent of the data subject.The processing of personal data, such as the name, address, e-mail address or telephone number of a data subject, is always in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation and in accordance with the country-specific privacy policy applicable to Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo. Through this privacy policy, our company seeks to inform the public about the nature, scope and purpose of the personal information we collect, use and process. Furthermore, data subjects are informed of their rights under this privacy policy.The Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo, as controller, has implemented numerous technical and organizational measures to ensure the most complete protection of personal data processed via this website. Nevertheless, Internet-based data transmissions can generally have security holes, so that absolute protection can not be guaranteed. For this reason, every person concerned is free to submit personal data to us in alternative ways, for example by telephone.1. Definitions The privacy policy of Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo is based on the terminology used by the European Directive and Regulatory Authority in the adoption of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). Our privacy policy should be easy to read and understand for the public as well as for our customers and business partners. To ensure this, we would like to explain in advance the terminology used.We use the following terms in this privacy policy, including but not limited to:a) Personal data Personal data is any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (hereinafter the “data subject”). A natural person is considered to be identifiable who, directly or indirectly, in particular by association with an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or one or more special features, expresses the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of this natural person can be identified.b) The person concerned Affected person is any identified or identifiable natural person whose personal data is processed by the controller.c) Processing Processing means any process or series of operations related to personal data, such as collecting, collecting, organizing, organizing, storing, adapting or modifying, reading, querying, using, with or without the aid of automated procedures; disclosure by submission, dissemination or other form of provision, reconciliation or association, restriction, erasure or destruction.d) Restriction of processing Restriction of the processing is the marking of stored personal data with the aim to limit their future processing.e) Profiling Profiling is any kind of automated processing of personal data that consists in using that personal information to evaluate certain personal aspects relating to a natural person, in particular aspects relating to job performance, economic situation, health, personal To analyze or predict preferences, interests, reliability, behavior, whereabouts or relocation of that natural person.f) Pseudonymisation Pseudonymisation is the processing of personal data in such a way that personal data can no longer be attributed to a specific data subject without the need for additional information, provided that such additional information is kept separate and subject to technical and organizational measures to ensure that the personal data not assigned to an identified or identifiable natural person.(g) Controller or controller The controller or controller is the natural or legal person, public authority, body or body that, alone or in concert with others, decides on the purposes and means of processing personal data. Where the purposes and means of such processing are determined by Union law or the law of the Member States, the controller or the specific criteria for his designation may be provided for under Union or national law.h) Processor The processor is a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body that processes personal data on behalf of the controller.i) Receiver Recipient is a natural or legal person, agency, agency or other entity to whom Personal Data is disclosed, whether or not it is a third party. However, authorities which may receive personal data under Union or national law in connection with a particular mission are not considered as beneficiaries.j) Third parties Third is a natural or legal person, public authority, body or body other than the data subject, the controller, the processor and the persons authorized under the direct responsibility of the controller or the processor to process the personal data.k) Consent Consent is any voluntarily given and unambiguously expressed in the form of a statement or other unambiguous confirmatory act by the data subject for the particular case, by which the data subject indicates that they consent to the processing of the personal data concerning him / her is.2. Name and address of the controller The person responsible within the meaning of the General Data Protection Regulation, other data protection laws in the Member States of the European Union and other provisions of a data protection character is:Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo Spinciceva 2D 21000 Split Croatia Tel .: +38521571203 Email: This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. Website: www.navisyachtcharter.com3. Cookies The websites of Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo use cookies. Cookies are text files that are stored and stored on a computer system via an Internet browser.Many websites and servers use cookies. Many cookies contain a so-called cookie ID. A cookie ID is a unique identifier of the cookie. It consists of a string through which Internet pages and servers can be assigned to the specific Internet browser in which the cookie was stored. This allows visited websites and servers to distinguish the individual’s browser from other internet browsers that contain other cookies. A particular web browser can be recognized and identified by the unique cookie ID. By using cookies, Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo can provide users of this website with more user-friendly services that would not be possible without cookies.By means of a cookie the information and offers on our website can be optimized in the sense of the user. Cookies allow us, as already mentioned, to recognize the users of our website. The purpose of this recognition is to make it easier for users to use our website. For example, the user of a website that uses cookies need not reenter their credentials each time they visit the website, as this is done by the website and the cookie stored on the user’s computer system. Another example is the cookie of a shopping basket in the online shop. The online shop remembers the items that a customer has placed in the virtual shopping cart via a cookie.The data subject can prevent the setting of cookies through our website at any time by means of a corresponding setting of the Internet browser used and thus permanently contradict the setting of cookies. Furthermore, already set cookies can be deleted at any time via an internet browser or other software programs. This is possible in all common internet browsers. If the data subject deactivates the setting of cookies in the Internet browser used, not all functions of our website may be fully usable.4. Collecting general data and information The website of the Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo collects a series of general data and information each time the website is accessed by an affected person or an automated system. This general data and information is stored in the log files of the server. The (1) browser types and versions used, (2) the operating system used by the accessing system, (3) the internet page from which an accessing system accesses our website (so-called referrers), (4) the sub-web pages which can be accessed via (5) the date and time of access to the website, (6) an Internet Protocol address (IP address),When using this general data and information, the Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo does not draw conclusions about the person concerned. Rather, this information is required to (1) correctly deliver the contents of our website, (2) to optimize the content of our website and to advertise it, (3) to ensure the continued functioning of our information technology systems and the technology of our website, and ( 4) to provide law enforcement authorities with the information necessary for law enforcement in the event of a cyberattack. This anonymously collected data and information are therefore statistically and further evaluated by Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo with the aim of increasing data protection and data security in our company. to ultimately ensure the best possible level of protection of the personal data we process. The anonymous data of the server log files are stored separately from all personal data provided by an affected person.5. Registration on our website The data subject has the possibility to register on the website of the data controller by providing personal data. The personal data to be sent to the controller is derived from the respective input mask used for the registration. The personal data entered by the data subject shall be collected and stored solely for internal use by the controller and for his own purposes. The controller may initiate the transfer to one or more processors, such as a parcel service, who also collects personal data solely for internal use,By registering on the website of the controller, the IP address assigned by the Internet service provider (ISP) of the data subject, the date and time of registration are also stored. The storage of this data takes place against the background that only so the misuse of our services can be prevented, and these data in case of need make it possible to clarify committed offenses. In this respect, the storage of this data is required to secure the controller. A disclosure of these data to third parties is not, unless there is a legal obligation to pass on or the disclosure of law enforcement serves.By registering the data subject voluntarily providing personal data, the data controller serves to provide the data subject with content or services that, due to the nature of the case, can only be offered to registered users. Registered persons are free to modify the personal data given at registration at any time or to delete it completely from the database of the data controller.The controller shall, at any time upon request, provide information to each data subject as to which personal data about the data subject is stored. Furthermore, the data controller corrects or deletes personal data at the request or reference of the data subject, insofar as this does not conflict with any statutory storage requirements. All data subjects of the controller are available to the data subject as a contact person in this context.6. Subscription to our newsletter On the Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo website, users are given the opportunity to subscribe to our company newsletter. Which personal data are transmitted to the data controller when the newsletter is ordered results from the input mask used for this purpose.The Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo informs its customers and business partners at regular intervals by way of a newsletter about offers of the company. The newsletter of our company can only be received by the data subject if (1) the data subject has a valid email address and (2) the data subject registers for the newsletter. For legal reasons, a confirmation e-mail will be sent to the e-mail address entered by an affected person for the first time for newsletter mailing using the double-opt-in procedure. This confirmation email is used to check whether the owner of the e-mail address as the person concerned authorized the receipt of the newsletter.When subscribing to the newsletter, we also store the IP address of the computer system used by the person concerned at the time of registration, as well as the date and time of registration, as assigned by the Internet Service Provider (ISP). The collection of this data is necessary in order to understand the (possible) misuse of an affected person’s e-mail address at a later date and therefore serves as legal safeguards for the controller.The personal data collected in the context of registering for the newsletter will be used exclusively to send our newsletter. Subscribers to the newsletter may also be notified by e-mail if this is necessary for the operation of the newsletter service or registration, as might be the case in the event of changes to the newsletter or technical changes. There will be no transfer of the personal data collected as part of the newsletter service to third parties. Subscription to our newsletter may be terminated by the person concerned at any time. The consent to the storage of personal data that the data subject has given us for the newsletter dispatch can be revoked at any time. For the purpose of revoking the consent, there is a corresponding link in each newsletter. It is also possible to unsubscribe from the newsletter at any time, directly on the controller’s website, or to inform the controller in a different way.7. Newsletter tracking The newsletters of the Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo contain so-called counting pixels. A counting pixel is a miniature graphic that is embedded in such emails that are sent in HTML format to enable log file recording and log file analysis. This allows a statistical evaluation of the success or failure of online marketing campaigns. Based on the embedded pixel, the Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo can detect if and when an e-mail was opened by an affected person and which links in the e-mail were accessed by the affected person.Such personal data collected via the counting pixels contained in the newsletters will be stored and evaluated by the controller in order to optimize the delivery of newsletters and to better adapt the content of future newsletters to the interests of the data subject. This personal data will not be disclosed to third parties. Affected persons are at any time entitled to revoke the separate declaration of consent made via the double-opt-in procedure. After revocation, this personal data will be deleted by the controller. A cancellation of the receipt of the newsletter, the Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo automatically interpreted as a revocation.8. Contact via the website The website of Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo contains information required by law to enable us to contact our company quickly and to communicate with us directly, which also includes a general address of the so-called electronic mail (e-mail address) , If an affected person contacts the data controller by e-mail or through a contact form, the personal data provided by the data subject will be automatically saved. Such personal data, voluntarily transmitted by an individual to the controller, is stored for the purpose of processing or contacting the data subject.9. Routine deletion and blocking of personal data The controller shall process and store the personal data of the data subject only for the period necessary to achieve the purpose of the storage or, as the case may be, by the European directives or regulations or by any other legislator in laws or regulations which the controller was provided for.If the storage purpose is omitted or if a storage period prescribed by the European directives and regulations or any other relevant legislator expires, the personal data will be routinely blocked or deleted in accordance with the statutory provisions.10. Rights of the data subject a) Right to confirmation Each data subject has the right, as granted by the European Regulators and Regulators, to require the controller to confirm whether personal data relating to him / her is being processed. If an affected person wishes to make use of this right of confirmation, they can contact an employee of the controller at any time. b) Right to information Any person concerned by the processing of personal data shall have the right, granted by the European Di- rective and Regulatory Authority, at any time to obtain from the data controller information free of charge on the personal data stored about him and a copy of that information. Furthermore, the European legislator and regulator has provided the data subject with the following information:– the processing purposes – the categories of personal data being processed – the recipients or categories of recipients to whom the personal data have been disclosed or are yet to be disclosed, in particular to recipients in third countries or to international organizations – if possible, the planned duration for which the personal data will be stored or, if that is not possible, the criteria for determining that duration – the existence of a right to rectification or erasure of the personal data concerning him or of a restriction of the processing by the person responsible or of a right to object to such processing – the existence of a right of appeal to a supervisory authority – if the personal data are not collected from the data subject: All available information on the source of the data – the existence of automated decision-making including profiling under Article 22 (1) and (4) of the GDPR and – at least in these cases – meaningful information on the logic involved and the scope and intended impact of such processing on the data subjectIn addition, the data subject has a right of access as to whether personal data has been transmitted to a third country or to an international organization. If that is the case, then the data subject has the right to obtain information about the appropriate guarantees in connection with the transfer.If an interested party wishes to exercise this right to information, they may at any time contact an employee of the controller.c) Right to rectification Any person affected by the processing of personal data has the right granted by the European legislator to demand the immediate correction of inaccurate personal data concerning him / her. Furthermore, the data subject has the right to request the completion of incomplete personal data, including by means of a supplementary declaration, taking into account the purposes of the processing.If an affected person wishes to exercise this right of rectification, they may, at any time, contact an employee of the controller.d) Right to cancellation (right to be forgotten) Any person affected by the processing of personal data shall have the right granted by the European Directives and Regulators to require the controller to immediately delete the personal data concerning him, provided that one of the following reasons is satisfied and the processing is not required:The personal data has been collected for such purposes or otherwise processed for which they are no longer necessary. The data subject withdraws the consent on which the processing was based in accordance with Article 6 (1) (a) of the GDPR or Article 9 (2) (a) of the GDPR and lacks any other legal basis for the processing. The data subject objects to the processing in accordance with Art. 21 (1) DS-GVO, and there are no legitimate reasons for the processing, or the data subject objects according to Art. 21 (2) DS-GVO Processing. The personal data were processed unlawfully. The erasure of personal data is necessary to fulfill a legal obligation under Union or national law to which the controller is subject. The personal data were collected in relation to information society services offered pursuant to Art. 8 para. 1 DS-GVO. If any of the above reasons are correct and an affected person wishes to arrange for the deletion of personal data stored at Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo, they may, at any time, contact an employee of the controller. The employee of the Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo will arrange for the extinguishing request to be fulfilled immediately.If the personal data has been made public by Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo and if our company is responsible for deleting personal data in accordance with Art. 17 para. 1 DS-GVO, the Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo is taken into consideration the technology available and the implementation costs, including technical means to inform other data controllers processing the published personal data that the data subject has deleted all links to them from those other data controllers personal data or copies or replicas of such personal data unless the processing is required.The employee of the Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo will arrange the necessary in individual cases.e) Right to restriction of processing Any person affected by the processing of personal data has the right, granted by the European directive and regulatory authority, to require the controller to restrict the processing if one of the following conditions applies:The accuracy of the personal data is contested by the data subject for a period of time that enables the controller to verify the accuracy of the personal data. The processing is unlawful, the data subject refuses to delete the personal data and instead requests the restriction of the use of personal data. The controller no longer needs the personal data for the purposes of processing, but the data subject requires them to assert, exercise or defend legal claims. The person concerned has objection to the processing acc. Art. 21 para. 1 DS-GVO and it is not yet clear whether the legitimate reasons of the person responsible outweigh those of the person concerned. If one of the above conditions is met and an affected person wishes to request the restriction of personal data stored at Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo, they may at any time contact an employee of the controller. The employee of the Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo will initiate the restriction of the processing.f) Data transferability Any person affected by the processing of personal data shall have the right conferred by the European Directives and Regulations to obtain the personal data concerning him / her provided to a controller by the data subject in a structured, common and machine-readable format. It also has the right to transfer this data to another person responsible without hindrance by the controller to whom the personal data was provided, provided that the processing is based on the consent pursuant to Article 6 (1) (a) of the GDPR or Article 9 (1) (b) 2 (a) of the GDPR or on the basis of a contract pursuant to Article 6 (1) (b) of the GDPR and that the processing is carried out by automated means;Furthermore, in exercising their right to data portability under Article 20 (1) of the GDPR, the data subject has the right to obtain that the personal data are transmitted directly from one controller to another, insofar as this is technically feasible and if so this does not affect the rights and freedoms of others.In order to assert the right to data portability, the data subject may at any time contact an employee of Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo.g) Right to object Any person implicated in the processing of personal data has the right granted by the European directives and regulations donor, for reasons arising from their specific situation at any time to the processing concerning them of personal data on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1 letter e or f DS-GVO takes an objection. This also applies to profiling based on these provisions.The Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo no longer process the personal data in the event of contradiction, unless we can prove compelling legitimate grounds for processing, outweigh the interests, rights and freedoms of the data subject, or the processing is used to Assertion, exercise or defense of legal claims.If the Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo processes personal data in order to operate direct mail, the data subject has the right at any time to object to the processing of personal data for the purpose of such advertising. This also applies to the profiling, as far as it is associated with such direct mail. If the data subject objects to Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo processing for direct marketing purposes, Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo will no longer process the personal data for these purposes.In addition, the data subject has the right, for reasons arising from his / her particular situation, against the processing of personal data concerning him / her, for scientific or historical research purposes or for statistical purposes pursuant to Art. 89 of the Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo Para. 1 DS-BER, objections are made, unless such processing is necessary to fulfill a task of public interest.In order to exercise the right of opposition, the data subject may directly contact any Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo or any other employee. The data subject is also free, in the context of the use of information society services, notwithstanding Directive 2002/58 / EC, to exercise his right of opposition by means of automated procedures using technical specifications.h) Automated decisions in individual cases including profiling Any person concerned by the processing of personal data shall have the right, as granted by the European legislature and the legislature, not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling, which has a legal effect on it or, in a similar manner, significantly affects it; unless the decision (1) is necessary for the conclusion or performance of a contract between the data subject and the controller, or (2) under Union or Member State legislation to which the controller is subject,is permitted and that such legislation contains appropriate measures to safeguard the rights, freedoms and legitimate interests of the data subject; or (3) with the express consent of the data subject.If the decision (1) is required for the conclusion or performance of a contract between the data subject and the controller or (2) it is done with the express consent of the data subject, the Navis Yacht Charter NYC / Posada doo shall take appropriate measures to assert the rights and liberties and the legitimate interests of the data subject, including at least the right to obtain the intervention of a person by the controller, to express his / her own position and to contest the decision.If the data subject wishes to claim automated decision-making rights, they can contact an employee of the controller at any time.i) Right to revoke a data protection consent Any person affected by the processing of personal data has the right, granted by the European directive and regulatory authority, to revoke consent to the processing of personal data at any time.If the data subject wishes to assert their right to withdraw consent, they may, at any time, contact an employee of the controller.11. Data protection in applications and in the application process The controller collects and processes the personal data of applicants for the purpose of processing the application process. The processing can also be done electronically. This is particularly the case if an applicant submits corresponding application documents to the controller by electronic means, for example by e-mail or via a web form available on the website. If the controller concludes a contract of employment with an applicant, the data transmitted will be stored for the purposes of the employment relationship in accordance with the law. If no employment contract with the candidate is concluded by the controller, For example, the application documents will be automatically deleted two months after notification of the rejection decision, provided that deletion does not conflict with any other legitimate interests of the controller. Other legitimate interest in this sense, for example, a burden of proof in a procedure under the General Equal Treatment Act (AGG).12. Legal basis of processing Art. 6 I lit. A DS-GMO serves our company as the legal basis for processing operations where we obtain consent for a particular processing purpose. If the processing of personal data is necessary to fulfill a contract of which the data subject is a party, as is the case, for example, in processing operations necessary for the supply of goods or the provision of any other service or consideration, processing shall be based on Art. 6 I lit. b DS-GMO. The same applies to processing operations that are necessary to carry out pre-contractual measures, for example in cases of inquiries regarding our products or services. If our company is subject to a legal obligation which requires the processing of personal data, such as the fulfillment of tax obligations, the processing is based on Art. 6 I lit. c DS-GMO. In rare cases, the processing of personal data may be required to protect the vital interests of the data subject or another natural person. This would be the case, for example, if a visitor to our premises were injured and his or her name, age, health insurance or other vital information would have to be passed on to a doctor, hospital or other third party. Then the processing would be based on Art. 6 I lit. d DS-GMO are based. Ultimately, processing operations could be based on Art. 6 I lit. f DS-GMOs are based. On this legal basis, processing operations that are not covered by any of the above legal bases are required if processing is necessary to safeguard the legitimate interests of our company or a third party, unless the interests, fundamental rights and fundamental freedoms of the person concerned prevail. Such processing operations are particularly allowed to us because they have been specifically mentioned by the European legislator. In that regard, it considered that a legitimate interest could be assumed if the data subject is a customer of the controller (recital 47, second sentence, DS-BER). if processing is necessary to safeguard the legitimate interests of our company or a third party, provided the interests, fundamental rights and fundamental freedoms of the person concerned do not prevail. Such processing operations are particularly allowed to us because they have been specifically mentioned by the European legislator. In that regard, it considered that a legitimate interest could be assumed if the data subject is a customer of the controller (recital 47, second sentence, DS-BER). if processing is necessary to safeguard the legitimate interests of our company or a third party, provided the interests, fundamental rights and fundamental freedoms of the person concerned do not prevail. Such processing operations are particularly allowed to us because they have been specifically mentioned by the European legislator. In that regard, it considered that a legitimate interest could be assumed if the data subject is a customer of the controller (recital 47, second sentence, DS-BER).13. Beneficial interests in the processing that are being pursued by the controller or a third party Is the processing of personal data based on Article 6 I lit. f DS-GMO is our legitimate interest in conducting our business for the benefit of all of our employees and our shareholders.14. Duration for which the personal data is stored The criterion for the duration of the storage of personal data is the respective statutory retention period. After the deadline, the corresponding data will be routinely deleted, if they are no longer required to fulfill the contract or to initiate a contract.15. Legal or contractual provisions for the provision of personal data; Necessity for the conclusion of the contract; Obligation of the data subject to provide the personal data; possible consequences of non-provision We clarify that the provision of personal data is partly required by law (eg tax regulations) or can also result from contractual provisions (eg information about the contracting party). Occasionally it may be necessary for a contract to be concluded that an affected person provides us with personal data that must subsequently be processed by us. For example, the data subject is required to provide us with personal information when our company enters into a contract with her. Failure to provide the personal data would mean that the contract with the person concerned could not be closed. Prior to any personal data being provided by the person concerned, the person concerned must contact one of our employees. Tweet
HomeBookingSitemapCharterLuxury Yachts Croatia Sailing Yachts CroatiaCatamarans CroatiaSailing Yachts GreeceCatamarans GreeceGulets CroatiaLuxury YachtsGreece CharterMediterranean CharterCrewed Sailing Yachts GreeceLuxury Sailing Yachts MediterraneanFeaturedItinerary & DestinationsItinerarySuggested Sailing Routes in CroatiaSuggested itinerary for South-central DalmatiaSuggested itinerary for North DalmatiaSuggested itinerary for GreeceDestinationsYacht charter BahamasYacht charter CaribbeanYacht charter Italy and FranceYacht charter SpainYacht charter TurkeyAboutNYC
About NYCCareersYacht ManagementTerms, Conditions & Contracts
TermsConditionsMYBA ContractHYBA ContractAdditional Information
About CroatiaMarinas in CroatiaAbout GreeceLinksVIP ServicesExecutive protectionVIP carsPrivate jet servicesEvents CharteringNewsContact Us
